

SKILLS

- Typescript
- CSS
- React
- Node
- Web APIsstyled-components
- Tailwind CSS
- React Router
- React Query
- SPA
- Webpack
- Vite
- React testing library

EDUCATION

09/2015 - 06/2019

Mordovian State University
| Saransk
Bachelor of Computer

Science

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced (C1)

Russian

Native

German Bulavkin

- 381621257346
- thewhitehaven04@gmail.com
- Ćirpanova 13, Novi Sad, Serbia 21101
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/german-bulavkin-866546

WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

https://github.com/thewhitehaven04

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A front-end engineer passionate about learning how things work under the hood, web application performance and delivering the best user experience. My vast background in quality assurance will help you bridge the gap in understanding between engineering teams and quality assurance.

WORK HISTORY

03/2024 - 12/2024

Front-End developer Stenn International | Remote

- Feature development for back-office clients
- Migrated the product's team features to the internal design system UI kit
- Collaborated with UX and UI designers to implement design changes

12/2022 - 02/2024

QA automation engineer Stenn International

- · Conducted UI and API automated testing with Pytest
- Optimised product team testing practices and coverage

04/2020 - 12/2022

QA automation engineer
IBS Appline | Moscow, Russia

- Performed UI and API testing of web- and SAP-based applications;
- · Refined testing policies, procedures and scripts

07/2019 - 02/2020

OA Engineer

Bytex LLC | Saransk, Russia

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

Computer hardware